[
  {	"id": 1, "qnum": 1,
    "question": "Who originally developed Javascript?",
    "answer1": "Douglas Crockford",
    "answer2": "Brendan Eich",
    "answer3": "Ryan Dahl",
    "answer4": "Jeremy Ashkenas",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2, "qnum": 2,
    "question": "What was the very first original name of Javascript?",
    "answer1": "LiveScript",
    "answer2": "ECMAScript",
    "answer3": "CoffeeScript",
    "answer4": "Mocha",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 3, "qnum": 3,
    "question": "Which one of these is not known as a Javascript framework?",
    "answer1": "Meteor",
    "answer2": "Angular",
    "answer3": "Backbone",
    "answer4": "Django",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 4, "qnum": 4,
    "question": "Javascript was originally influenced by all of the following except which language?",
    "answer1": "Python",
    "answer2": "Java",
    "answer3": "Ruby",
    "answer4": "C",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 5, "qnum": 5,
    "question": "Fill in the blank: Javascript is currently the ____ language on Github.",
    "answer1": "most-used",
    "answer2": "second most-used",
    "answer3": "third most-used",
    "answer4": "fourth most-used",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {	"id": 6, "qnum": 1,
    "question": "Who has the most triple doubles in NBA history?",
    "answer1": "Magic Johnson",
    "answer2": "Jason Kidd",
    "answer3": "Oscar Robertson",
    "answer4": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 7, "qnum": 2,
    "question": "Who has scored the most total points in NBA history?",
    "answer1": "Kobe Bryant",
    "answer2": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    "answer3": "Karl Malone",
    "answer4": "Michael Jordan",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8, "qnum": 3,
    "question": "Who has the most total assists in NBA history?",
    "answer1": "Steve Nash",
    "answer2": "John Stockton",
    "answer3": "Jason Kidd",
    "answer4": "Mark Jackson",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9, "qnum": 4,
    "question": "Who has the most total rebounds in NBA history?",
    "answer1": "Elvin Hayes",
    "answer2": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    "answer3": "Bill Russell",
    "answer4": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 10, "qnum": 5,
    "question": "Which organization has won the most NBA championships?",
    "answer1": "San Antonio Spurs",
    "answer2": "Chicago Bulls",
    "answer3": "Boston Celtics",
    "answer4": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {	"id": 11, "qnum": 1,
    "question": "Which American football team has won the most championships?",
    "answer1": "Green Bay Packers",
    "answer2": "San Francisco 49ers",
    "answer3": "Chicago Bears",
    "answer4": "New York Giants",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 12, "qnum": 2,
    "question": "Which quarterback holds the record for most career passing yards?",
    "answer1": "Dan Marino",
    "answer2": "Peyton Manning",
    "answer3": "Tom Brady",
    "answer4": "Brett Favre",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 13, "qnum": 3,
    "question": "Which player holds the record for most career rushing yards?",
    "answer1": "Barry Sanders",
    "answer2": "Emmitt Smith",
    "answer3": "Walter Payton",
    "answer4": "LaDainian Tomlinson",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14, "qnum": 4,
    "question": "Which quarterback holds the record for the most passing yards in a single season?",
    "answer1": "Drew Brees",
    "answer2": "Tom Brady",
    "answer3": "Dan Marino",
    "answer4": "Peyton Manning",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 15, "qnum": 5,
    "question": "Who is the head coach of the San Francisco 49ers?",
    "answer1": "Pete Caroll",
    "answer2": "Steve Kerr",
    "answer3": "Jim Harbaugh",
    "answer4": "Tony Sparano",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {	"id": 16, "qnum": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following was not invented in the United States?",
    "answer1": "light bulb",
    "answer2": "gunpowder",
    "answer3": "washing machine",
    "answer4": "telephone",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17, "qnum": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following is not one of the three main branches of the United States government?",
    "answer1": "judicial",
    "answer2": "legislative",
    "answer3": "executive",
    "answer4": "senate",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 18, "qnum": 3,
    "question": "How many states are there?",
    "answer1": "48",
    "answer2": "50",
    "answer3": "52",
    "answer4": "54",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19, "qnum": 4,
    "question": "Which person has never been Vice President of the United States?",
    "answer1": "George H.W. Bush",
    "answer2": "Bill Clinton",
    "answer3": "Al Gore",
    "answer4": "Dan Quayle",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20, "qnum": 5,
    "question": "Which person has never been President of the United States?",
    "answer1": "John Adams",
    "answer2": "James Madison",
    "answer3": "Benjamin Franklin",
    "answer4": "Andrew Jackson",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }
]
